soprano.com 2013-05-20

# Soprano.com Privacy Policy

Last modified: April 13, 2012 

**Information we collect**

We collect information in two ways:

Information you give us.

Information we get from your use of other companies, like Facebook and Google (e.g. Google Analytics). This information includes:

Device information

We may collect device-specific information (such as your hardware model, operating system version, unique device identifiers).

Internet protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and referral URL.  

Cookies and anonymous identifiers

**How we use information we collect**

We use information collected from cookies and other technologies, like pixel tags, to improve your user experience and the overall quality of our services. For example, by saving your language preferences, we'll be able to have our services appear in the language you prefer.

Information we share

We do not share personal information with companies, organizations and individuals outside of Soprano.com unless one of the following circumstances apply:

With your consent

We will share personal information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of Soprano.com when we have your consent to do so. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information.

**Information security**

We work hard to protect Google and our users from unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of information we hold. In particular:

We encrypt many of our services using SSL.

**Application**

Our Privacy Policy applies to all of the services offered by Soprano.com.

Our Privacy Policy does not apply to services offered by other companies or individuals, including products or sites that may be displayed to you in our websites, or other sites linked from our services. Our Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of other companies and organizations who advertise our services, and who may use cookies, pixel tags and other technologies to serve and offer relevant ads.

Changes

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time.
